[{"answer": "So, Jim, Im really nervous about this presentation I have to give at work nex", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Yeah, I always get nervous too when I have to give a presentation.  How man", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 19, "question": "So, Jim, Im really nervous about this presentation I have to give at work nex", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " I think there will be about 50 people in the audience", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Yeah, I always get nervous too when I have to give a presentation.  How man", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Thats a pretty big crowd", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 24, "question": " I think there will be about 50 people in the audience", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " I know.  Thats whats making me a little nervous", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Thats a pretty big crowd", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " What kind of presentation is it", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I know.  Thats whats making me a little nervous", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 27, "question": " What kind of presentation is it", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " You know.  Is it a demonstration, a briefing, a workshop, etc.", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 28, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Oh, its a demonstration", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 32, "question": " You know.  Is it a demonstration, a briefing, a workshop, etc.", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Why are you so nervous", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Oh, its a demonstration", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Well, Ive never given a presentation to such a large group of people before.  ", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Why are you so nervous", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Have you been preparing already", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Well, Ive never given a presentation to such a large group of people before.  ", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " A little bit.  Ive made an outline of what I want to say and wrote down som", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Have you been preparing already", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " You should definitely prepare some kind of visual aids.  Things like a power poin", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 43, "question": " A little bit.  Ive made an outline of what I want to say and wrote down som", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " OK.  Ive got both of those things.  I just need to finish up the power poin", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 47, "question": " You should definitely prepare some kind of visual aids.  Things like a power poin", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " You should check the venue too.  That way youll know what it looks like, and yo", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 51, "question": " OK.  Ive got both of those things.  I just need to finish up the power poin", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Oh, thats a good point.  I guess I should make sure the microphone, computer", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 55, "question": " You should check the venue too.  That way youll know what it looks like, and yo", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Definitely.  You dont want to get in there and have technical problems.  How ar", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Oh, thats a good point.  I guess I should make sure the microphone, computer", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I was thinking of telling an anecdote first to get the audiences attention an", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Definitely.  You dont want to get in there and have technical problems.  How ar", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " That sounds good.  Dont forget to tell the audience whether they should hold thei", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": " I was thinking of telling an anecdote first to get the audiences attention an", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " I didnt even think about that.  Thanks.  Ill add that.  Is there anything I shoul", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 70, "question": " That sounds good.  Dont forget to tell the audience whether they should hold thei", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Well, I guess first of all make sure that the audience can hear you.  Make sure yo", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 74, "question": " I didnt even think about that.  Thanks.  Ill add that.  Is there anything I shoul", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " I could do a sound check at the beginning", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Well, I guess first of all make sure that the audience can hear you.  Make sure yo", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Thats a good idea.  Then, remember to make eye contact with the audience.  Yo", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 79, "question": " I could do a sound check at the beginning", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " I remember I used to turn my back to the audience sometimes when I wa", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Thats a good idea.  Then, remember to make eye contact with the audience.  Yo", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yeah, dont do that.  The only other thing I can think of is to smile and try not t", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 90, "question": " I remember I used to turn my back to the audience sometimes when I wa", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Ill have to try to remember not to do that", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Yeah, dont do that.  The only other thing I can think of is to smile and try not t", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Thats pretty much all I can think of.  Why dont you finish preparing th", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Ill have to try to remember not to do that", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Oh, that would be great!  Thanks, Jim", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Thats pretty much all I can think of.  Why dont you finish preparing th", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " Sure.  Once you practice it a few times, youll feel more comfortable and les", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Oh, that would be great!  Thanks, Jim", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " I hope so", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 105, "question": " Sure.  Once you practice it a few times, youll feel more comfortable and les", "qSentId": 104},{"answer": " Youll do fine, I know", "docId": "03-08", "aSentId": 106, "question": " I hope so", "qSentId": 105}]
